<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on Notes From a Human - a blog by Luan James</title><link>https://notesfromahuman.dev/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Notes From a Human - a blog by Luan James</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.148.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://notesfromahuman.dev/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>First Human Note</title><link>https://notesfromahuman.dev/posts/250729_first_human_note/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://notesfromahuman.dev/posts/250729_first_human_note/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hi!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m Luan James, and this is the first post of a project I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to start for a long time.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I believe we’re living in a &lt;strong>very significant moment in human history&lt;/strong> — a time that makes me reflect on what our lives will look like in a few years, as AI becomes more and more embedded in everything we do.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you ask me, I don&amp;rsquo;t really know what the world will look like in a couple of years. For now, I just want to reflect on it — and adapt to this new reality as it unfolds.&lt;/p></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hi!</p>
<p>I&rsquo;m Luan James, and this is the first post of a project I&rsquo;ve wanted to start for a long time.</p>
<p>I believe we’re living in a <strong>very significant moment in human history</strong> — a time that makes me reflect on what our lives will look like in a few years, as AI becomes more and more embedded in everything we do.</p>
<p>If you ask me, I don&rsquo;t really know what the world will look like in a couple of years. For now, I just want to reflect on it — and adapt to this new reality as it unfolds.</p>
<p>For context, I&rsquo;m a software developer with over 10 years of experience. Over the years, I&rsquo;ve seen many changes in how we build software — but nothing compares to what we’re experiencing now. AI is game-changing for software development, and <strong>I don’t think everyone has fully realized that yet</strong>. That’s the main reason I started this blog.</p>
<p>As a senior engineer, one of the key expectations is to mentor others, support them in their careers, and help guide people in the right direction. That’s what I hope to do here.</p>
<p><em>What’s next on this blog?</em></p>
<p>I know your time is limited, and no one wants to read another super long blog post from some random guy on the internet. So my goal is to share short reflections — just a few thoughts that take no more than five minutes of your time. I want to help you, my fellow human developer, better understand <strong>how to use AI effectively in your day-to-day work</strong>. That’s what you can expect from the upcoming posts.</p>
<p>If I ever write longer articles, I’ll publish them on my <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/luanjames">LinkedIn</a>.</p>
<p>Thanks for reading this note from a human.</p>
<p>– Luan</p>
]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>